{
    "subject": "resource/Don_Davis_(composer)",
    "predicate": "property/occupation",
    "object": "resource/Film_composer",
    "human_readable": "Don Davis is a film composer.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9755606651306152,
            "question": "Is Don Davis known for composing music for films?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9596046805381775,
            "question": "What makes Don Davis a successful film composer?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9303522109985352,
            "question": "Can you name some films for which Don Davis has composed music?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8933202028274536,
            "question": "What awards or recognition has Don Davis received for his film composing?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8532131314277649,
            "question": "What kind of music does Don Davis compose?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8291560411453247,
            "question": "Has Don Davis composed music for any other types of media besides films?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7898774743080139,
            "question": "Are there any specific genres of film music that Don Davis is known for?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5864616632461548,
            "question": "How has Don Davis's music impacted the films he has worked on?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5617997050285339,
            "question": "What profession does Don Davis have?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.37635207176208496,
            "question": "What is Don Davis's contribution to the world of film scoring?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Don Davis is a film composer.",
            "html": "dbpedia_4970_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What profession does Don Davis have?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4970_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=How has Don Davis's music impacted the films he has worked on?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4970_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Are there any specific genres of film music that Don Davis is known for?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4970_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4970_24.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4970_25.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4970_26.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4970_35.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4970_49.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4970_56.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4970_6.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4970_72.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4970_74.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4970_8.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "The query about Don Davis being a film composer can be evaluated as follows:\n\n* The documents mention that Don Davis is a \"virtuoso film and television composer\" (file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_4970/re-ranker-msmarco/26.txt, 72.txt), indicating that he has worked in the film industry.\n* The documents also mention that Don Davis has composed music for films such as \"The Matrix\" and \"Jurassic Park II\", further supporting his association with film composition.\n* Additionally, one of the documents mentions that Don Davis has released an album called \"Warriors Of Virtue: Original Motion Picture Score (2023)\", which is a score for a movie.\n\nGiven this information, the answer to whether Don Davis is a film composer is:\n\n```\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThe documents provide multiple instances that support the statement \"Don Davis is a film composer.\" For example, they mention his work on film scores such as \"Main Title / Trinity Infinity\" from The Matrix and other films like \"Jurassic Park II,\" \"Tiny Toons Adventures,\" and \"Bound.\""
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}